[{"answer": "What's wrong with our car", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pen.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "We don't use it", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "We don't use it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pen.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "If you were using it, we wouldn't use it", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Plus the insurance", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pen.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "How could you not get the insurance", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "my friend.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pen.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "You don't need the air conditioner. So, you have your speech all ready", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "God it's so hot in here. Why don't you put on the air conditioning", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pen.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "It's not a speech. Do I have to make a speech", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "He likes looking", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pen.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "But how long can you look", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "What do you have to go scuba diving for", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pen.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "For fun", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pen.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I did NOT have a coke", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Did you have a coke or what", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pen.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Somebody had a coke", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "See? You know your father. He can't get a write to the penny, but that's why he was such a good president.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pen.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "This pen", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "I couldn'", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pen.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I can't take it", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "No, I'm not..", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pen.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I cannot take it", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Take the pen", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pen.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Take the pen", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Because you made such a big fuss about it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pen.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "You shouldn't have said anything. What did you expect him to do?", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Come in", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pen.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Why is it so hot in here? How can they sleep like this", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Then YOU would be hunched over", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pen.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "You can't go", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Hi. How are you", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pen.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "my friend, this is my friend", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "You know my friend, you've got a hell of a nerve taking that kid's pen", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pen.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "His pen", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Don't worry about it! I'll give it back", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pen.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "I don't want it", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Isn't he supposed to be the emcee", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pen.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Well. This should be a very interesting evening", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": " Uh... What about those muscle relaxers?  ", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pen.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Say what?  Say what", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "He gave it to me", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pen.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "I'm not sitting down!", "qsentId": 44}]